var preguntas=[


{
"pregunta":"0",
"respuesta":"ARO"
},


{
"pregunta":"1",
"respuesta":"TE"
},

{
"pregunta":"2",
"respuesta":"ÑU"
},

{
"pregunta":"3",
"respuesta":"HUMO"
},

{
"pregunta":"4",
"respuesta":"OCA"
},

{
"pregunta":"5",
"respuesta":"OLA"
},

{
"pregunta":"6",
"respuesta":"OSO"
},

{
"pregunta":"7",
"respuesta":"UFO"
},

{
"pregunta":"8",
"respuesta":"AJO"
},

{
"pregunta":"9",
"respuesta":"BIO"
},
{
"pregunta":"10",
"respuesta":"TORO"
},


{
"pregunta":"11",
"respuesta":"DADO"
},

{
"pregunta":"12",
"respuesta":"DINO"
},

{
"pregunta":"13",
"respuesta":"TRÉBOL"
},

{
"pregunta":"14",
"respuesta":"DUQUE"
},

{
"pregunta":"15",
"respuesta":"CORAZÓN"
},

{
"pregunta":"16",
"respuesta":"TIZA"
},

{
"pregunta":"17",
"respuesta":"TIJERA"
},

{
"pregunta":"18",
"respuesta":"TEJA"
},

{
"pregunta":"19",
"respuesta":"TAPIA"
}


];
